

Atlanta, GA

**609.892.2662** 

<u>msjoyjackson@gmail.com</u>

in www.linkedin.com/in/joysjackson

www.github.com/joydotcom

**Profile** 

Passionate, Devoted, and Personable Creative with an extensive successful background in Education, Design, and Performance Art. Possessing Leadership, Cultural Competence, and Innovative transferable skill sets. Combining my Software Engineering certificate and uniquely creative professional experiences.

Education

Georgia Tech – Full Stack Web Development Certificate - 2021

William Paterson University – Educational Leadership 18 Graduate Credits - 2018

Montclair State University - B.Sc Kinesiology - 2008

Experience

## Teacher Leader, Ben Hill Private Academy: Atlanta, GA – 2019 - 2020

- Observed & Evaluated Academic and Social Development of Students
- Managed Teaching Staff
- Parent Liaison

## Student Development Coordinator/ Teacher: NJ Public Schools - 2009 - 2019

- Implemented, Facilitated & Instructed school-wide (750+) SEAL Curriculum
- Wrote and presented Proposals and Budgets for Community Outreach
- Analyzed, Prepared, and Presented Evidence Data
- Performance Art & Design Teacher (700 students weekly)

## Asst. Manager PT: Nightlife Talent: Atlantic City Casinos & Resorts - 2007 -2015

- Coordinated Scheduling and Managed Rehearsals for Nightlife Talent
- 93% Talent Satisfaction Rate

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Node, VS Code, MVC, SQL, Github, Adobe Suite, FrontEnd Design, Team Management, Leadership, Adaptability, Personable, Culturally Conscious, Customer Service, Effective Communication, Attention to Detail, Budget & Proposal Writing, Critical Thinking, Problem Solving, Creativity, Organization, Empathy

Tech Projects

Personal Professional Portfolio - <u>Designer</u> - React.js, Bootstrap, GitHub, VS Code <a href="http://www.msjoyjackson.com">http://www.msjoyjackson.com</a> | <a href="https://github.com/Joydotcom/react-portfolio">https://github.com/Joydotcom/react-portfolio</a>

**Local Roots** - <u>Designer</u> - *React.js, Bootstrap, Adobe XD, SQL, VSC* : Marketplace for plant lovers.

https://damp-reef-27856.herokuapp.com/ https://github.com/julesscheil/Local-Roots

**GamerZ** - <u>Designer</u> - *JavaScript, CSS, HTML, VS Code* : Community for Gamers <u>https://afternoon-garden-82475.herokuapp.com/</u> | https://github.com/greenkimparsons/gamerz